thinkseer.com 2019-05-05

# Privacy and Cookie Policy | Seer Interactive

Seer Interactive is committed to the privacy of our customers and users of this website. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Seer Interactive uses, maintains, and discloses information collected from users of this website, including but not limited to any tools or services offered thereon (together, the “Website”). It only governs information collected online through our Website, not to information collected offline. By using the Website, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy. THIS WEBSITE IS NOT DIRECTED AT OR INTENDED FOR USE BY CHILDREN UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE.

## Information You Provide to Us

Seer Interactive may request or collect personal information from visitors to the Website in a variety of ways, including through online forms (such as our Contact Us) form and through Google Analytics, which collects demographic information of visitors to the Website. “Personal Information” means information that identifies or reasonably may identify a natural person, and might include:

  * Your name
  * Your phone number(s)
  * Your email address(es)
  * Your place of employment
  * Your job title
  * Your location

Personal Information does not include aggregate information to the extent an individual’s identity cannot reasonably be determined from such information.

Generally, Personal Information is requested when: (i) you request information about Seer Interactive products and services via the Website; (ii) you subscribe to a newsletter or e-mail lists; or (iii) you utilize other tools or services available via the Website. If you fail to provide the requested Personal Information, you may not be able to access all or portions of the Website or purchase products and services.

The transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure and, therefore, Seer Interactive cannot guarantee the security of the data you transmit to our website; any such transmission is at your own risk.  

## Information Collected Automatically Through Cookies and Similar Technologies

When you visit the Website, email us, or download our mobile applications, we collect information sent to us by your computer, mobile phone, or other access device, some of which may be deemed Personal Information. For example, Seer Interactive may collect information about how visitors to our website access the website using a tracking ID unique to each visitor through the use of cookies. Cookies are pieces of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For session ID cookies, once you close your browser or log out, the cookie terminates and is erased. Session ID cookies may be used by us to track user preferences while the user is visiting the website. They also help to minimize load times and save on server processing. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on your computer’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies may be used by us to store certain information. Your browser’s help file contains information and instructions for removing persistent cookies. Cookies used on the Seer Interactive website do not contain Personal Information.

Seer Interactive may also collect information anonymously about how visitors to the Website access the Website through the use of web beacons, and similar technologies. That information may include IP addresses, the region or general location of a computer or device accessing the internet, browser type, operating system, page view history, and other usage information.

## Information Collected Automatically Through Log Files

Like most standard websites, we use log files. Information written into log files may include the following: internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser type; internet service provider (ISP); device ID or unique identifier; device type; geo-location information; computer and connection information; mobile network information; referring/exit pages; platform type; date/time stamp; and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.  However, none of the information stored in our log files, including but not limited to IP addresses, is linked to Personal Information.

## Information Collected Through Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google. Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of our Website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. Seer Interactive may implement certain tracking features supported by Google Analytics for Display Advertising Demographics and Interest Reporting. The data collected (age and gender) is used to better understand our visitors and help us provide the most relevant content we can. Seer Interactive may also employ Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. Third-party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on sites across the Internet. Seer Interactive and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies and third-party cookies together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone’s past visits to our Website. You can opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and/or customize Google Display Network ads using the Google Ads Settings or Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. We will not facilitate the merging of Personal Information with non-personally identifiable information previously collected from Display Advertising features that is based on the DoubleClick cookie unless you have provided Seer Interactive with prior affirmative (i.e., opt-in) consent to such merger. 

For more information regarding Google Analytics’ privacy practices please visit www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html.

## Social Media

Seer Interactive may also receive certain information that’s stored or processed by social media services or other third party platforms, such as Facebook, or other third-party social media plug-ins, integrations and applications. These features may collect your IP address as well as details of the pages you are visiting on the Website. Each social media platform may have its own privacy notices that specifically govern its use of social media features.

## How We Use and Share the Information We Collect

Seer Interactive will use the information you provide to respond to your inquiry or provide any services requested by you, including without limitation requests for newsletters and notifications. Seer Interactive may also use Personal Information and share it with trusted third parties to provide the requested services or for research purposes regarding the effectiveness of our website services, marketing, advertising and sales efforts. Any such third-party sharing is subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations. WE WILL NOT SELL YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES OR IN ANY WAY SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH A THIRD PARTY FOR A THIRD PARTY’S MARKETING PURPOSES, UNLESS YOU SPECIFICALLY AUTHORIZE SUCH INFORMATION SHARING. 

Seer Interactive may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from users to trusted third parties, investors and potential partners. In such cases, only statistical information will be disclosed and Personal Information will be kept strictly confidential. In the event Seer Interactive is sold, the information collected from users may be transferred to the new owners. We may from time to time engage third parties to preserve, analyze, or otherwise store or manipulate data received by us from our customers. In all such cases, third party service providers will be required to treat all such data with the same degree of care as Seer Interactive and they will be prohibited from disclosing such data to any other person or party, except as otherwise provided for in this Privacy Policy. 

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose Personal Information when required by law or if we have a good-faith belief that disclosure is necessary and required to comply with legal process served on Seer Interactive or to protect your safety and security or the safety and security of others, including Seer Interactive.

## Newsletters and Informational Emails

If you sign up for our newsletter, you will occasionally receive newsletters or e-mails with information about our company and the services we offer. You always have the opportunity to opt out of receiving any further newsletters or emails.

## Third Party Links

Our Website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Seer Interactive is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The Seer Interactive Privacy Policy as described herein applies solely to information collected by Seer Interactive. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our Website and welcome any feedback about any of the websites we link to.

## Cross-Border Information Transfers

You acknowledge (a) that the Website is based in the United States, (b) that any information or data is provided to a company in the United States, and (c) that Seer Interactive must adhere to laws of the United States. You agree that Personal Information collected on the Website will be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Seer Interactive, its affiliates, partners, service providers, or agents maintain facilities, and while in such jurisdictions may be subject to access pursuant to the laws of those jurisdictions. Each of these countries has different privacy laws that afford varying levels of protection for your Personal Information, and such laws may be less stringent or may not be as comprehensive as those laws that exist in your country.

## Transfer

Seer Interactive partners with and occasionally hires other companies to provide services on its behalf. Personal Information may be shared with these companies; however, we will only share your Personal Information to accomplish the purposes for which we collected the Personal Information, subject to a written agreement ensuring that they will maintain the confidentiality of your Personal Information and prohibiting them from using that information for any other purpose.

## Access

Upon an individual’s request, if feasible or applicable, Seer Interactive will offer individuals from whom it collects Personal Information reasonable access to their Personal Information and will afford such individuals a reasonable opportunity to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate Personal Information. Seer Interactive may limit or deny access to Personal Information where providing such access would be unreasonably burdensome or expensive under the circumstances or as otherwise permitted under relevant law. Where required by law, Seer Interactive will also offer such individuals a reasonable opportunity to delete Personal Information, subject to any rights or obligations Seer Interactive has to retain such Personal Information.

## Security

Seer Interactive will take reasonable measures including technical, physical, and administrative measures and training, as appropriate, to protect Personal Information it collects and processes from loss, misuse, and unauthorized disclosure, access, alteration, and destruction. Such measures apply generally across Seer Interactive systems, services, and facilities and to those third party systems and services which are utilized by Seer Interactive to provide the Website. Seer Interactive safeguards information according to established security standards and periodically assesses new technology for methods of protecting information. However, Seer Interactive cannot guarantee the security of Personal Information.

## Data Retention

Seer Interactive generally keeps Personal Information only for as long as we believe necessary for the purpose for which it was collected, or as permitted by law.

## Data Integrity

Seer Interactive will take reasonable measures to verify that Personal Information it collects and processes is relevant for its intended use, reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete, and current.

## Enforcement and Dispute Resolution

Seer Interactive will conduct periodic assessments to confirm the accuracy of, and verify its adherence to, this Privacy Policy. Seer Interactive will investigate suspected infractions and will take all appropriate action. Any questions, concerns, or complaints concerning the collection and use of Personal Information by Seer Interactive should be directed to privacy@seerinteractive.com.

Seer Interactive will conduct a reasonable investigation into and will attempt to resolve any complaints in accordance with the principles contained in this Policy. Complaints that cannot be resolved between Seer Interactive and the complainant shall be resolved via binding arbitration with the American Arbitration Association in accordance with its Commercial Arbitration Rules and Mediation Procedures. Complainants seeking arbitration must send written notice to the Seer Interactive General Counsel at SEER Interactive, 1033 North 2nd Street, 2nd Floor, Philadelphia PA 19123. A single arbitrator will be selected by Seer Interactive and the arbitration will be held in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Each party will pay its own costs associated with the arbitration and agrees to split the arbitration fees. Solely with respect to complaints by Seer Interactive employees that cannot be resolved internally, Seer Interactive agrees to work with the relevant Data Protection Authority, if applicable, to resolve such matter.

## Limitations

Seer Interactive’s adherence to this Privacy Policy may be limited by any applicable legal, regulatory, ethical, or public interest consideration, and as expressly permitted or required by any applicable law, rule, or regulation.  SEER Interactive may need to retain your information for a period of time in order to continue providing a service to you, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, prevent fraud, enforce our customer or user agreement, or take other actions as required or permitted by law. In addition, Seer Interactive reserves the right to disclose Personal Information reasonably related to the sale or disposition of all or part of its business.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Seer Interactive reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a new Privacy Policy on its Website, and you agree that it is your responsibility to review updates to this Privacy Policy.

## Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding the disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to privacy@seerinteractive.com or write to us:

Privacy  
SEER Interactive  
1033 North 2nd Street, 2nd Floor  
Philadelphia PA 19123

## Additional Privacy Rights for Individuals in the European Union

In addition to the rights described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, you may have additional rights pursuant to applicable data protection legislation. If you are an individual in the European Union (EU), these rights may include the right to information portability, the right to withdraw consent for processing, the right to object to or restrict the processing of your Personal Information, and the right to file a complaint with the supervisory authority of the EU country in which you reside.

## Questions

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or your own Personal Information, please send an email to privacy@seerinteractive.com. 

Last modified: October 1, 2018
